Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم الإدارة، شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
(What could have happened)
(ما كان يمكن أن يحدث)
(to make you drink yourself into such sorrow?)
(لجعلك تغرق في هذا الحزن بالشراب؟)
You are drunk.
أنت ثمل.
I'm drunk.
أنا ثمل.
You're drunk too.
أنت ثمل أيضاً.
We are both drunk.
كلانا ثمل.
Isn't that better?
أليس هذا أفضل؟
♪Whom have I ever failed♪
♪من خذلتُ يوماً؟♪
♪Incense burns through a few sticks can the rest of my life be redeemed?♪
♪يحترق البخور حتى آخر عود، فهل يمكن إنقاذ ما تبقى من حياتي؟♪
(They used Yunqi to test me.)
(لقد استخدموا يونكي لاختباري.)
(They must already suspect me.)
(لا بد أنهم يشكون بي بالفعل.)
♪Unwilling to forgive past mistakes♪
♪غير راغب في مسامحة أخطاء الماضي♪
♪Blaming myself for not protecting our vows as I should have♪
ألوم نفسي لعدم حماية عهودنا كما ينبغي.
(If life and death are uncertain,)
(إذا كانت الحياة والموت غير مؤكدين،)
(I might as well follow my heart)
(ربما من الأفضل أن أتبع قلبي)
(and live in this moment.)
(وعش هذه اللحظة.)
♪Counting sorrow carefully who stayed by my side through hardship♪
♪أحصي الأحزان بعناية، أولئك الذين بقوا بجانبي في الشدائد♪
♪There will eventually be a pure land where all karmic burden is cast away♪
♪ستكون هناك في النهاية أرض طاهرة حيث يتم التخلص من كل عبء كارمي♪
♪Not until worldly splendor fades♪
♪لن يحدث ذلك إلا بعد أن يزول بريق الدنيا♪
♪Can one understand what cuts to the bone♪
هل يستطيع المرء أن يفهم ما يمزق العظم؟
♪At dusk, with white hair, I still cannot fathom destiny♪
♪عند الغسق، بشعر أبيض، ما زلتُ عاجزاً عن فهم القدر♪
You like me.
أنت تحبني.
Am I right?
هل أنا على صواب؟
♪Where blossoms fall, I'm glad the fragrance in our hearts stays the same♪
♪حيثما تتساقط الأزهار، يسعدني أن العطر في قلوبنا يبقى كما هو♪
♪Youth slips away♪
♪الشباب يتلاشى♪
♪Just to wait for your once-in-a-thousand-years glance♪
♪فقط في انتظار نظرتك التي لا تتكرر إلا مرة كل ألف عام♪
♪Dreams wander back to the old road where we met♪
♪تعود الأحلام إلى الطريق القديم حيث التقينا♪
♪Watching you gently play the zither♪
♪أشاهدك وأنت تعزف على آلة الزيثارة برفق♪
♪Time rests upon the strings♪
♪الزمن يستقر على الأوتار♪
♪Waiting for someone to brew a pot of tea♪
♪أنتظر من يُعدّ لي إبريق شاي♪
Do you know what you are doing?
هل تعلم ما تفعله؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
Then do you know who I am?
هل تعرف من أنا؟
You?
أنت؟
The great Governor of Liang.
الحاكم العظيم لسلالة ليانغ.
The treacherous official everyone reviles.
المسؤول الخائن الذي يكرهه الجميع.
You know this,
أنت تعلم هذا،
yet you still throw yourself at me?
ومع ذلك ما زلتِ ترمين نفسكِ عليّ؟
My hands are also stained with blood.
يداي ملطختان بالدماء أيضاً.
I am a ghost bearing a blood feud.
أنا شبح يحمل ضغينة دموية.
You and I
أنت وأنا
are a match made
هما ثنائي مثالي
in heaven.
في الجنة.
♪After countless struggles across the waters♪
♪بعد صراعات لا حصر لها عبر المياه♪
♪At last the lotus heart awakens♪
♪أخيرًا يستيقظ قلب اللوتس♪
♪Drifting across three lifetimes♪
♪انجراف عبر ثلاثة أعمار♪
♪Just to wait for your once-in-a-thousand-years glance♪
♪فقط في انتظار نظرتك التي لا تتكرر إلا مرة كل ألف عام♪
♪The distant mountains fade along the path home♪
تتلاشى الجبال البعيدة على طول الطريق المؤدي إلى المنزل.
♪I walk with you through morning bells and evening drums♪
♪أسير معك عبر أجراس الصباح وطبول المساء♪
♪Our story lies in the mountains like an ink-washed immortal painting♪
قصتنا تكمن في الجبال كلوحة خالدة مغسولة بالحبر.
♪After countless struggles across the waters♪
♪بعد صراعات لا حصر لها عبر المياه♪
♪At last the lotus heart awakens♪
♪أخيرًا يستيقظ قلب اللوتس♪
♪Drifting across three lifetimes♪
♪انجراف عبر ثلاثة أعمار♪
♪Just to wait for your once-in-a-thousand-years glance♪
♪فقط في انتظار نظرتك التي لا تتكرر إلا مرة كل ألف عام♪
♪The distant mountains fade along the path home♪
تتلاشى الجبال البعيدة على طول الطريق المؤدي إلى المنزل.
♪I walk with you through morning bells and evening drums♪
♪أسير معك عبر أجراس الصباح وطبول المساء♪
♪Our story lies in the mountains like an ink-washed immortal painting♪
قصتنا تكمن في الجبال كلوحة خالدة مغسولة بالحبر.
♪Where blossoms fall, I'm glad the fragrance in our hearts stays the same♪
♪حيثما تتساقط الأزهار، يسعدني أن العطر في قلوبنا يبقى كما هو♪
♪Youth slips away just to wait for your once-in-a-thousand-years glance♪
♪تتلاشى الشباب في انتظار نظرة خاطفة لا تتكرر إلا مرة كل ألف عام♪
You're drunk.
أنت ثمل.
I won't let you wake up with regrets.
لن أدعك تستيقظ نادماً.
Sleep.
ينام.
♪Time rests upon the strings♪
♪الزمن يستقر على الأوتار♪
♪Waiting for someone to brew a pot of tea♪
♪أنتظر من يُعدّ لي إبريق شاي♪
=The Architect=
=المهندس المعماري=
=Episode 20= (We're both drunk, isn't that great?)
=الحلقة 20= (كلانا ثمل، أليس هذا رائعًا؟)
Miss.
يفتقد.
You asked me to get some snacks.
طلبت مني أن أحضر بعض الوجبات الخفيفة.
But inside the snack box, there's this thing.
لكن داخل علبة الوجبات الخفيفة، يوجد هذا الشيء.
It's Young Master's jade pendant.
إنها قلادة اليشم الخاصة بالسيد الشاب.
Master placed it on him.
وضعها السيد عليه.
They made a move.
لقد قاموا بخطوة.
(No. 29, East Exit) Xiao Huaijin is
(رقم 29، المخرج الشرقي) هو شياو Huaijin
using Yunqi to trick me.
يستخدم يونكي لخداعي.
I'm just
أنا فقط
one step away from finding Yunqi.
خطوة واحدة تفصلنا عن العثور على يونكي.
Is the Young Master
هل السيد الشاب
really there?
هل هو موجود فعلاً؟
Xiao Huaijin
شياو هواجين
is likely luring me in.
من المحتمل أن يكون هذا ما يغريني.
Like shooting fish in a barrel.
كأنها صيد سمك في برميل.
He thinks he is setting a trap.
يظن أنه ينصب فخاً.
But he didn't know
لكنه لم يكن يعلم
I'm letting him do it.
سأتركه يفعل ذلك.
This is
هذا هو
my chance to find Yunqi.
فرصتي للعثور على يونكي.
Miss,
يفتقد،
what do we do now?
ماذا نفعل الآن؟
Stay put.
ابقَ في مكانك.
We watch from the shadows.
نراقب من الظلال.
I've tracked him for days.
لقد تتبعته لأيام.
Every day is the same.
كل يوم هو نفسه.
I couldn't find a way
لم أجد طريقة
to confirm
للتأكيد
which is the real Xiao Huaijin.
وهو شياو هوايجين الحقيقي.
Xiao Huaijin is hollowed out by debauchery.
لقد أُفرغت شياو هوايجين من روحها بسبب الفجور.
He is weak inside,
إنه ضعيف من الداخل،
unlike a martial artist.
على عكس ممارس فنون الدفاع عن النفس.
His steps are floating
أتباعه يطفون
and powerless.
وعاجز.
That's him.
هذا هو.
The real him.
هو نفسه الحقيقي.
It's too dangerous.
الأمر خطير للغاية.
I will go with you.
سأذهب معك.
Xiao Huaijin doesn't know
شياو هواجين لا يعرف
I've found him.
لقد وجدته.
I'll scout ahead.
سأقوم بالاستطلاع مسبقاً.
I need you to do something more important.
أحتاج منك أن تفعل شيئاً أكثر أهمية.
- My Lord.
- سيدي.
Be alert.
كن متيقظاً.
Be cautious.
كن حذراً.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
(Xiao Huaijin hid Yunqi)
(شياو Huaijin اختبأ Yunqi)
(in General Li's old residence.)
(في مقر إقامة الجنرال لي القديم.)
(No wonder Pei Yu couldn't find any leads.)
(لا عجب أن باي يو لم يتمكن من العثور على أي خيوط.)
Stand there.
قف هناك.
Put down the basket.
ضع السلة.
Go in.
ادخل.
Hurry up.
أسرع.
Yunqi.
يونكي.
Stand back!
تراجعوا!
What do you want?
ماذا تريد؟
What do you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
I advise you not to come closer.
أنصحك بعدم الاقتراب أكثر.
Swords have no eyes.
السيوف ليس لها عيون.
Let her go.
اسمح لها أن تذهب.
If you want a fight,
إذا كنت تريد شجاراً،
fight me.
تحداني.
Pei Yu.
باي يو.
His Majesty ordered you to hunt the Shen's fugitive.
أمرك جلالته بمطاردة الهارب من عائلة شين.
Yet here you are sheltering them.
لكنك هنا تقوم بإيوائهم.
How
كيف
should His Majesty punish you?
هل ينبغي لجلالته أن يعاقبك؟
I see
أرى
no Shen's fugitive here.
لا يوجد هارب من شين هنا.
But you, you are killing the innocents.
لكن أنت، أنت تقتل الأبرياء.
Even if I kill you here,
حتى لو قتلتك هنا،
His Majesty won't hold me accountable.
لن يحاسبني جلالته.
Is that so?
هل هذا صحيح؟
You will have to survive me first.
عليك أن تنجو مني أولاً.
Release her,
أطلق سراحها،
and I will leave your corpse intact.
وسأترك جثتك سليمة.
Intact?
متصل؟
You think you are in a position to negotiate?
أتظن أنك في وضع يسمح لك بالتفاوض؟
Fine.
بخير.
I shall offer you one more chance.
سأمنحك فرصة أخرى.
You die.
تموت.
She lives.
إنها على قيد الحياة.
What do you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
Fine.
بخير.
As you wish.
كما تشاء.
Take care of yourself.
اعتنِ بنفسك.
Pei Yu!
باي يو!
Take care of my brother.
اعتني بأخي.
Xiao Huaijin.
شياو هواجين.
I'll take you down with me!
سأسقطك معي!
No!
لا!
(End of Episode)
(نهاية الحلقة)
The rest is up to Heaven's will.
والباقي متروك لمشيئة السماء.
If the Governor doesn't wake
إذا لم يستيقظ الحاكم
before the lamp burns out,
قبل أن ينطفئ المصباح،
I'm afraid...
أخشى...
Pei Yu gave his life
ضحى باي يو بحياته
to save you.
لإنقاذك.
Surely you are willing
بالتأكيد أنت مستعد
to give everything for him?
أن أضحي بكل شيء من أجله؟
Give methe Immortal Herb.
أعطني العشبة الخالدة.
I'll give you my life.
سأهب لك حياتي.
♪Loneliness♪
♪الوحدة♪
♪How do I cross it?♪
♪كيف أعبرها؟♪
♪Whom have I ever failed♪
♪من خذلتُ يوماً؟♪
♪Incense burns through a few sticks♪
♪يحترق البخور من خلال بضع أعواد♪
♪Can the rest of my life be redeemed?♪
هل يمكن إصلاح ما تبقى من حياتي ؟
♪The flowing years pass through desolation♪
♪تمر السنين المتدفقة عبر الخراب♪
♪Unwilling to forgive past mistakes♪
♪غير راغب في مسامحة أخطاء الماضي♪
♪Blaming myself for not protecting♪
ألوم نفسي لعدم حمايتي لنفسي.
♪Our vows as I should have♪
♪عهودنا كما ينبغي أن تكون♪
♪Sorrow♪
♪حزن♪
♪Counting it carefully♪
♪أحصيها بعناية♪
♪Who stayed by my side through hardship♪
♪من بقي بجانبي في الشدائد♪
♪There will eventually be a pure land♪
♪ستكون هناك أرض طاهرة في نهاية المطاف♪
♪Where all karmic burden is cast away♪
♪حيث تُزال كل الأعباء الكارمية♪
♪Not until worldly splendor fades♪
♪لن يحدث ذلك إلا بعد أن يزول بريق الدنيا♪
♪Can one understand what cuts to the bone♪
هل يستطيع المرء أن يفهم ما يمزق العظم؟
♪I still cannot fathom destiny♪
♪ما زلتُ عاجزاً عن فهم القدر♪
♪After countless struggles across the waters♪
♪بعد صراعات لا حصر لها عبر المياه♪
♪At last the lotus heart awakens♪
♪أخيرًا يستيقظ قلب اللوتس♪
♪Drifting across three lifetimes♪
♪انجراف عبر ثلاثة أعمار♪
♪Just to wait for your once-in-a-thousand-years glance♪
♪فقط في انتظار نظرتك التي لا تتكرر إلا مرة كل ألف عام♪
♪The distant mountains fade along the path home♪
تتلاشى الجبال البعيدة على طول الطريق المؤدي إلى المنزل.
♪I walk with you through morning bells and evening drums♪
♪أسير معك عبر أجراس الصباح وطبول المساء♪
♪Our story lies in the mountains♪
قصتنا تكمن في الجبال
♪Like an ink-washed immortal painting♪
♪كلوحة خالدة مغسولة بالحبر♪
♪Where blossoms fall♪
♪حيث تتساقط الأزهار♪
♪I'm glad the fragrance in our hearts stays the same♪
♪أنا سعيد لأن العطر في قلوبنا يبقى كما هو♪
♪Youth slips away♪
♪الشباب يتلاشى♪
♪Just to wait for your once-in-a-thousand-years glance♪
♪فقط في انتظار نظرتك التي لا تتكرر إلا مرة كل ألف عام♪
♪Dreams wander back to the old road where we met♪
♪تعود الأحلام إلى الطريق القديم حيث التقينا♪
♪Watching you gently play the zither♪
♪أشاهدك وأنت تعزف على آلة الزيثارة برفق♪
♪Time rests upon the strings♪
♪الزمن يستقر على الأوتار♪
♪Waiting for someone to brew a pot of tea♪
♪أنتظر من يُعدّ لي إبريق شاي♪